[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The redunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the medium cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Redunknown"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Metal"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the medium brick cube heavier than the medium BlueUnknown cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium brick cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large wood cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium brick cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium blueunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium RedUnknown cube travel to quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large wood cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium RedUnknown cube collide with the large wood cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium brick cube collide with the large wood cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium blueunknown cube and the medium brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube and the medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The large wood cube and the medium blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium brick cube and the large wood cube"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium brick cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium brick cube and the medium blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium blueunknown cube and the medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The large wood cube and the medium blueunknown cube"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Will the large wood cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]